http://www.unitedaccess.com/privacy-policy/

Sales: 877-501-8267EspañolHours & DirectionsRecently ViewedstarnotificationsACCOUNTUnited AccessSearchlensFilterlensNew InventoryAll Accessible VehiclesSchedule a Test DriveSchedule a Home DemoVehicle Trade-InUsed InventoryAll Used InventoryCurrent PromotionVehicle SpecialsAs-Is Wheelchair Vans for SaleNon-Adapted VehiclesSchedule a Test DriveSchedule a Home DemoVehicle Trade-InProductsConversionsWhat is a Van Conversion?Compare Converted VehiclesChrysler Wheelchair VansDodge Wheelchair VansFord Wheelchair SUVsHonda Wheelchair VansToyota Wheelchair VansWheelchair Accessible VansWheelchair & Scooter LiftsHandicap Vehicle SeatingWheelchair SecurementHandicap Driving AidsMobility ScootersCommercialCommercial InventoryCommercial Wheelchair VansSenior Care FacilitiesIndependent Living CentersAmbulette ParatransitNon-Emergency Medical TransportNon-Profit OrganizationsCommercial Wheelchair LiftsRentalsRentalsWheelchair Van Rental RatesVeterans Wheelchair Van Rental RatesResourcesAlly Wheelchair Van FinancingWheelchair Van FinancingHandicap Vehicle RebateVeteran ResourcesServiceWheelchair Van ServicePreventive Maintenance24/7 ServiceExtended Protection PlansAbout UsAbout UsFAQsMission and VisionDealership LocationsSupport VeteransNewsCareersTestimonialsPress InquiriesNMEDA/QAP CertificationContact UsPut Your Phone In ParklensclearAll Accessible VehiclesSchedule a Test DriveSchedule a Home DemoVehicle Trade-InAll Used InventoryCurrent PromotionVehicle SpecialsAs-Is Wheelchair Vans for SaleNon-Adapted VehiclesSchedule a Test DriveSchedule a Home DemoVehicle Trade-InConversionsConversionsWhat is a Van Conversion?Compare Converted VehiclesChrysler Wheelchair VansDodge Wheelchair VansFord Wheelchair SUVsHonda Wheelchair VansToyota Wheelchair VansWheelchair Accessible VansWheelchair & Scooter LiftsHandicap Vehicle SeatingWheelchair SecurementHandicap Driving AidsMobility ScootersCommercial InventoryCommercial Wheelchair VansSenior Care FacilitiesIndependent Living CentersAmbulette ParatransitNon-Emergency Medical TransportNon-Profit OrganizationsCommercial Wheelchair LiftsRentalsWheelchair Van Rental RatesVeterans Wheelchair Van Rental RatesAlly Wheelchair Van FinancingWheelchair Van FinancingHandicap Vehicle RebateVeteran ResourcesWheelchair Van ServicePreventive Maintenance24/7 ServiceExtended Protection PlansAbout UsFAQsMission and VisionDealership LocationsSupport VeteransNewsCareersTestimonialsPress InquiriesNMEDA/QAP CertificationContact UsPut Your Phone In ParkHomeNew InventoryUsed InventoryProductsCommercialRentalsResourcesServiceAbout UsSubmitCondition lensCondition lensexpand_moreexpand_lessMakes lensMakes lensexpand_moreexpand_lessModels lensModels lensexpand_moreexpand_lessTrims lensTrims lensexpand_moreexpand_lessConversion Manufacturer lensConversion Manufacturer lensexpand_moreexpand_lessConversion Model lensConversion Model lensexpand_moreexpand_lessPrice lensPrice lensexpand_moreexpand_lessYears lensYears lensexpand_moreexpand_lessMore FiltersMileage lensMileage lensexpand_moreexpand_lessColors lensColors lensexpand_moreexpand_lessExteriorInteriorBody lensBody lensexpand_moreexpand_lessFewer FiltersClear AllDoneShopAccountYou have no Recently Viewed or Saved Vehicles.Click here to begin your search.Saved VehiclesViewed VehiclesShow AllShow LessThe username or password provided is incorrect.Sign inForgot PasswordCreate an AccountLogging in...< BackReset PasswordPlease provide an email address.User does not exist.Please enter verification code.Verification code is not correct.Please enter a password.Password must have length greater than or equal to 6 and include uppercase, symbol and numeric characters.Reset PasswordSubmitting Request...< BackCreate an accountPlease provide an email address.Email address is already taken. You may have signed up already.Please enter a password.Password is not valid. Please make sure it is at least 8 characters long and contains at least an uppercase letter, a lowercase letter, a number, and a symbol.Passwords don't match. Please enter your passwords again.Please provide a first name.Please provide a last name.Sign UpSigning up...Welcome, Log OutLogging Out...ShopAccountYou have no Recently Viewed or Saved Vehicles.Click here to begin your search.Saved VehiclesViewed VehiclesShow AllShow LessThe username or password provided is incorrect.Sign inForgot PasswordCreate an AccountLogging in...< BackReset PasswordPlease provide an email address.User does not exist.Please enter verification code.Verification code is not correct.Please enter a password.Password must have length greater than or equal to 6 and include uppercase, symbol and numeric characters.Reset PasswordSubmitting Request...< BackCreate an accountPlease provide an email address.Email address is already taken. You may have signed up already.Please enter a password.Password is not valid. Please make sure it is at least 8 characters long and contains at least an uppercase letter, a lowercase letter, a number, and a symbol.Passwords don't match. Please enter your passwords again.Please provide a first name.Please provide a last name.Sign UpSigning up...Welcome, Log OutLogging Out...Submit United Access Privacy PolicyEffective Date: January 1, 2016Protecting the privacy of your personal information is important to us. We hope that these policies regarding your privacy (the “Privacy Policy” or “Policy”) demonstrate our commitment to making your experience on our Web site (the “Site”) thoroughly enjoyable.Individuals must be 13 years of age or older to use this Site and you warrant that you are 13 years of age or older. By using the Site, you consent to the privacy practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us. Therefore, you should carefully review this Policy so you understand our privacy practices.This Privacy Policy will inform you about:What information we collect from you;What “cookies” are and how they are used;Information concerning links to third party Web sites;Information for younger visitors and their parents;How we use the information we collect;Disclosure of information;The security measures we put in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of the information we obtain;How you may view the information we collect and update and correct the information; andRevisions to this Privacy PolicyA summary of the information we gather. As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected from your visit to our Site. If you choose to create an account or contact us via a form on this site, we collect personally identifiable information (“PII”) that you provide such as your name, street address, phone number, and e-mail address. Please enter your information carefully as we do not have the ability to update any changed information. The PII you submit will be used to carry out your requests, respond to your inquiries, and to notify you (if applicable) regarding any promotions.We also collect aggregate information that does not identify a specific individual. Aggregate information may include demographic information, the type of browser being used (e.g., Internet Explorer, Safari, Chrome, etc.), the operating system you are using (e.g., Vista, Windows 7/8, or Mac OS), the number of users that visit a specific page on the Site and the character and duration of such visits. This aggregate information may be used to help analyze Site traffic and improve our services. At no point, however, will the aggregated information personally identify you.Automatically Collected Information. We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you visit the Site, our systems automatically collect your IP address, and, as referenced above, the type of browser you use. Information may be automatically collected through the use of “cookies” which are discussed in more detail below. We may also collect information about your browsing behavior, such as entry and exit points for the Site, search terms, website addresses you visit, page views, and impressions.What are cookies and how do we use them? Cookies are small text files placed on your computer’s hard drive when you visit the Site. These files identify your computer and record your preferences and other data about your visit so that when you return to the site, the site knows who you are and can personalize your visit. In general, we use cookies to collect information so that we can determine how to improve our Site by seeing which areas, features and products are most popular, to personalize the site and improve the site experience. For example, collecting this information helps us streamline your experience on the Site–for example, by remembering who you are or “automatically” filling out forms for you. We also use this information to understand changes in consumer trends and demand, and to offer products and services to interested customers and demographic groups, thus improving the shopping experience. Most browsers automatically accept cookies as the default setting. You can modify the setting to reject cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit by editing browser options. If you decide not to accept our cookies, you will still be able to access those parts of our site available to the general public but you may not be able to use some of the Site’s features or services and you may have a less satisfactory experience.Internal Use of PII. In general, we use PII internally to serve our users or customers, to enhance and extend our customer and user relationships so our users or customers may take maximum advantage of our products and services. For example, by understanding how you use our Site from your computer or mobile device, we are able to customize and personalize your experience. More specifically, we use PII to provide services or to anticipate and resolve problems with our Site, or to respond to customer support inquiries, and to create and inform you of new products or services from United Access or others that may better meet your needs. You should review the following section to understand when United Access discloses PII to affiliated and non-affiliated third parties.The following section describes our disclosure practices more fully: Your PII may be used by us and our parent, subsidiaries, affiliates, joint venturers, successors, assigns, sponsors and/or partners (“Affiliated Third Parties”) to provide you with additional services. We may also rent, sell, or share your PII with other people or non-affiliated third parties.Internal Analysis. We may use PII and aggregate information for our own internal statistical, design, or operational purposes, such as to estimate our audience size, or measure aggregate traffic patterns as well as to understand demographic, customer interest, and other trends among our users. We may also use PII to customize various aspects of the Site to your preferences. We may outsource these tasks to third parties for external analysis.External Analysis.This Site uses Adobe® Site Catalyst to help United Access measure the use of the Site or tailor our online ads based on the likely interests of our users. You can opt out of the use of Adobe cookies for these purposes by clicking here: Opt Out.Marketing Purposes: As referenced above, we may disclose your PII to both Affiliated Third Parties and non-affiliated third parties so they can inform you about their products or services. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails.Our Affiliates: PII as well as aggregate information may be shared with our Affiliated Third Parties and stored on equipment and facilities that we share with such affiliates. We will keep all information collected from this Site logically separate from other information stored by such affiliates on such equipment.Business Transfers: Information about our users and the Site is one of our most important business assets. Therefore, information about our users, including PII, will be disclosed as part of any merger or acquisition, creation of a separate business to provide the Site or fulfill products, sale or pledge of company assets as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which PII would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company.Protection of United Access and Others: We release PII when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply our policies; to protect our rights or property, or to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, our Site; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay. In addition, we reserve the right to disclose any PII or aggregate information if required to do so by law, including compliance with legal process served on United Access, or if we believe that such action is necessary in order to (a) to protect or defend the legal rights or property of United Access, the Site, or its users; or (b) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of the Site’s users or the general public.Links to third party sites. The Site may contain hyperlinks to other Web sites, including sites we may not own or operate. We do not monitor or control the information collection or privacy practices of any third parties, and are not responsible for their practices or the content of their Web sites, including their use of any information (such as IP address, browser type, or operating system) collected when visitors “click through” links to their sites or view advertisements served by them. We encourage you to become familiar with their privacy practices, and to contact such third parties if you have any questions about their respective privacy policies.Children’s Privacy Policy. The Site is not intended for individuals under thirteen years of age. We do not permit use of the Site by anyone under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly, directly, or passively collect information from children under age 13. If you are under 13 years of age, you should stop using this Site.Do Not Track. Our Site does not respond to browser-based, DO NOT TRACK requests.Disclosure of handles and postings. The username you select or are provided with in order to participate in certain public areas (such as bulletin boards, chat rooms, and the like) of the Site (your “Handle”) is deemed non-personally identifiable information. Your Handle may be published on the Site and may be disclosed to others, including, without limitation, to the public at large, and to any third parties with whom we elect to share such information. In addition, if you include your name or any other PII in any material transmitted or posted on public areas of the Site, such information will be published on the Site and will be disclosed to other users of the Site and to other third parties who may have access to or otherwise see a display of such information. You hereby release, hold harmless and waive any claims against United Access relating to such disclosure, sharing, or publication.Security. Our data networks are protected by advanced firewall and password protection systems. We also maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of PII in our custody and control. We also are committed to employing reasonable technology in order to protect the security of our Site. Our security practices and policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals are granted access to the information provided by our visitors. There is no 100% guarantee of security on the Internet, however. In addition, e-mail that you send us is not necessarily secure against interception. You are ultimately responsible for the security of your user name and password. If you have to write it down, please keep your user name separate from your password.Revisions to policy. Please note that, by using the Site, you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Site. We may change or amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Policy. If we make any material changes to our Policy or how we handle your personal information, we will post an “update” notice to our site and change the date of the Policy. If we are going to use any PII in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the changes; your continued use of the Site subsequent to changes to this Privacy Policy will mean that you accept the changes; therefore, please bookmark this page and review it frequently. The “Effective Date” at the top of this Agreement will assist you in determining whether you have reviewed the most current version.However, if users have opted out of all communication with the Site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will PII be used in this new manner. We will use information in accordance with the most current Privacy Policy.
Enter Your Zip Code
Please enter a ZIP code or allow us to use your location to find vehicles near you that match your search criteria.
ZIP Code (5 digit US ZIP code)
Locate
OR
Use My Location
Sorry, we were not able to detect your location. Please enter a ZIP code to continue.
Try again
Your browser has blocked access to detect your location. Please enter a ZIP code to continue, or try
again after you grant access to detect your location.
Try again
We didn't recognize that ZIP code.
Please check it and try again.
Book Rental Form
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms. This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply. ×
Service Appointment Request Form
Fill out the form below and one of our friendly service representatives will contact you with an appointment confirmation or other scheduling options. Our service department staff is here to answer any questions and our qualified technicians can address your vehicle service needs.
Select Services(select all services that apply)Other ServicesI'm not sure what services I needMaintenance ServicesRegular Scheduled MaintenanceMobility Equipment InspectionOther ServiceVehicle InformationYear*Make*Model*TrimMileageSelect a LocationChoose Your State*Choose Closest State LocationArizonaArkansasColoradoIdahoIllinoisIowaKansasMississippiMissouriNebraskaNew MexicoNew YorkOklahomaOregonTennesseeTexasUtahChoose the Location Closest To You In Arizona*Make Selection Closest To YouChandlerScottsdaleChoose The Location Closest To You In Arkansas*Make Selection Closest To YouCape GirardeauSpringfieldChoose The Location Closest To You In Colorado*Make Selection Closest To YouColorado SpringsHighlands RanchWheat RidgeChoose The Location Closest To You In Idaho*Make Selection Closest To YouSalt Lake CityChoose The Location Closest To You In Illinois*Make Selection Closest To YouCape GirardeauSt. LouisFentonChoose The Location Closest To You In Iowa*Make Selection Closest To YouKansas CityLenexaChoose The Location Closest To You In Kansas*Make Selection Closest To YouKansas CityLenexaChoose The Location Closest To You In Mississippi*Make Selection Closest To YouMemphisChoose The Location Closest To You In Missouri*Make Selection Closest To YouCape GirardeauColumbiaKansas CityLenexaSpringfieldSt. LouisFentonChoose The Location Closest To You In Nebraska*Make Selection Closest To YouKansas CityLenexaChoose The Location Closest To You In New Mexico*Make Selection Closest To YouAlbuquerqueChoose The Location Closest To You In New York*Make Selection Closest To YouRochesterSyracuseChoose The Location Closest To You In Oklahoma*Make Selection Closest To YouOklahoma CityChoose The Location Closest To You In Oregon*Make Selection Closest To YouPortland EastPortland WestChoose The Location Closest To You In Tennessee*Make Selection Closest To YouMemphisChoose The Location Closest To You In Texas*Make Selection Closest To YouArlingtonAustinCarrolltonRowlettEl PasoChoose The Location Closest To You In Utah*Make Selection Closest To YouSalt Lake CitySelect Preferred Date and TimeThis is not a confirmed appointment until you get a confirmation call back from United AccessDate*
Time*
: HH
MM
AM PM
While Your Vehicle is Being Serviced*I plan to stay and wait for my vehicleI will drop off my vehicleI need a rentalContact InformationFirst Name*Last Name*Phone*Email*
AddressAddress 2CityStateZip*What Service Do You Need?If any issues come up, we will contact you immediately. We take privacy and data security seriously. Click to read our Privacy Policy.NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms. This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply. ×
